hacksplaining.com 2019-04-14

# Privacy

### Your privacy is critically important to us

At Hacksplaining we have a few fundamental principles: 

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. 
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights. 
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services. 

###### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Hacksplaining collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Hacksplaining’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Hacksplaining’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Hacksplaining may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website. 

###### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Hacksplaining’s websites choose to interact with Hacksplaining in ways that require Hacksplaining to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Hacksplaining gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask subscribers who sign up for Hacksplaining Site to provide an email address. Those who engage in transactions with Hacksplaining – by purchasing access to the service, for example – are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Hacksplaining collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Hacksplaining. Hacksplaining does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities. 

###### Aggregated Statistics

Hacksplaining may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, Hacksplaining may monitor the most popular exercises on the Hacksplaining Site. Hacksplaining may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Hacksplaining does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. 

###### Protection for Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Hacksplaining discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Hacksplaining’s behalf or to provide services available at Hacksplaining’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Hacksplaining’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Hacksplaining will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Hacksplaining discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Hacksplaining believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Hacksplaining, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of a Hacksplaining website and have supplied your email address, Hacksplaining may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Hacksplaining and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Hacksplaining takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information. 

###### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Hacksplaining uses cookies to help Hacksplaining identify and track visitors, their usage of Hacksplaining website, and their website access preferences. Hacksplaining visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Hacksplaining’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Hacksplaining’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies. 

###### Business Transfers

If Hacksplaining, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Hacksplaining goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Hacksplaining may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy. 

###### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Hacksplaining may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Hacksplaining’s sole discretion. Hacksplaining encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
